export const htmlQuizData = [
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "Which HTML tag is used for creating hyperlinks?",
        options: ["<link>", "<a>", "<href>", "<url>"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "In HTML, which tag is used for creating a table?",
        options: ["<table>", "<tr>", "<td>", "<th>"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'span' element in HTML?",
        options: ["Defines a section in a document", "Inline container for styling", "Defines a table row", "Defines a list item"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        options: ["Hypertext Markup Language", "Hypertext Markdown Language", "Hyperloop Machine Language", "Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborghinis"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'alt' attribute in an HTML image tag?",
        options: ["Alternate text for the image", "Alignment of the image", "Animation of the image", "Attribute of the image"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "Which HTML element is used for creating an unordered list?",
        options: ["<ol>", "<li>", "<ul>", "<dl>"],
        answer: 3
    },
  
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "Which HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?",
        options: ["class", "style", "id", "font"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What does the 'DOCTYPE' declaration in HTML do?",
        options: ["Defines the document type", "Defines a data type", "Defines a function type", "Defines a script type"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "Which HTML element is used for creating a form?",
        options: ["<input>", "<form>", "<button>", "<label>"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'header' element in HTML?",
        options: ["Defines a header for a document", "Defines a navigation link", "Defines a section in a document", "Defines a footer for a document"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'iframe' element in HTML?",
        options: ["Inline frame for external content", "Image container", "Interactive form", "Input field for text"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "Which HTML tag is used for creating an ordered list?",
        options: ["<ul>", "<li>", "<ol>", "<dl>"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'em' element in HTML?",
        options: ["Defines emphasized text", "Defines a strong importance", "Defines a subscript", "Defines a superscript"],
        answer: 1
    },
    
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'br' element in HTML?",
        options: ["Defines a bold text", "Defines a break line", "Defines a bullet point", "Defines a blockquote"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "Which HTML tag is used for creating an image?",
        options: ["<image>", "<img>", "<picture>", "<src>"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "Which HTML attribute is used to specify the character encoding of the HTML document?",
        options: ["charset", "encoding", "char-type", "meta"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "In HTML, which tag is used to create a hyperlink that opens in a new tab?",
        options: ["<a href='url' target='_blank'>", "<a href='url' target='_new'>", "<a href='url' new-tab>", "<a href='url' open-tab>"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'cite' element in HTML?",
        options: ["Defines a citation", "Defines a code element", "Defines a container", "Defines a center-aligned text"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "Which HTML tag is used to define the structure of an HTML document, including the head and body sections?",
        options: ["<structure>", "<layout>", "<html>", "<document>"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        title: "HTML",
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'sup' element in HTML?",
        options: ["Defines a superscript", "Defines a subscript", "Defines a bold text", "Defines a break line"],
        answer: 1
    },
];    